After that, we need to use a fixed needle to imitate the effect of compression by tightening the scarf part of the cut-off plate, but the fixed needle follows the grid point and in Marvelous Designer, once the
point of the cut-off plate is modified, the sewing line or the decrease or increase of the particle diameter will cause the fixed needle to be re-stripped and return to the time when there is no added fixed needle.
So before we add the fixed needle, we need to modify the content that will affect the grid. For example, delete the inner line that can not be used first.
When deleting the inner line, the grid changes too much, and the cut-off plate is not fixed.
So, we need to modify the content that will affect the grid. For example, delete the inner line that can not be used first.
So, we need to modify the content that will affect the grid.
In this case, we can reduce the particle diameter first.
After reducing it, we will remove the fixed needle and re-stripped it, but the grid will not affect too much.
Then we remove the inner line and modify it.
In addition, the two sides are fixed points.
In this case, the fixed needle on the cut-off plate will not move,
Then delete the sewing line, the sewing line will also affect the line of the net.
After deleting, simulate again.
Then continue to reduce the slope of the cut-off plate to 80, make the cut-off a little tighter.
Now the particle diameter of the cut-off plate has been reduced, so reduce the slope of the cut-off plate at the same time to make the cut-off have more grid surface, prevent protrusion.
Then we can freeze the cut-off plate, and then we will not modify it.
Then increase the slope of the cut-off plate to 45.
Reduce the particle diameter of the cut-off plate to 5, prevent instability.
Simulate to see if there is any instability.
Then continue to increase the slope of the cut-off plate to 50, do not increase too much at once.
When the slope is increased to 60, you will find that the cut-off plate has begun to be unstable.
Then continue to simulate, if there is instability, the best solution at this time is to simulate the plate of the cut-off element together.
Return to the time when there is no simulation, cut-off and then simulate together.
After the simulation is stable, continue to freeze the outer plate, and then do not cut-off.
Then slowly increase the slope according to the law of 5.
From 60 to 70 slowly, every time you modify, you must stabilize the simulation for more than 5 seconds, and then do it again.
Before it is 26, there is another reason, that is because of the slope just now, which is only returning to 60.
If you directly under these slopes, the power is frozen, with a constant strength to prevent interference.
In this rate, adding a fixed needle to prevent instability will cause the rate to return to 100 and the fixed needle to be too unnatural.
And when returning to the rate, the fixed needles on both ends are not deleted.
If these two fixed needles are deleted, their own gravity will pull the knot down and it will be unstable.
When the rate is increased to 75, it is unstable again.
At this time, we can go back to 70 and add a fixed needle to the squeezed part.
This time, we can add a fixed needle to the
one that is below the front view.
Since the fixed needle only selects the part that can be seen from the front view and cannot be selected to the back view,
we can only select a part of the frame to increase the density.
Add Stabilizer and increase the position compared to the 2D window.
You can choose the middle part first and then choose a larger part and gradually add the Stabilizer.
Rotate in different angles to ensure that you can see the part where the Stabilizer is hidden at every angle.
If not, continue to increase the Stabilizer.
If you are not sure of the position, you can also directly select a large part in the 2D window frame and then compare the position of the 3D window.
Do not add a large piece of Stabilizer at once, so that the subsequent simulation will be too stiff.
Add Stabilizer and increase the position of the Stabilizer.
When adding Stabilizer, it is better to test the patience and add it little by little.
Don't add too much, it's better to add quickly.
Add Stabilizer and increase the position of the Stabilizer.
As long as you ensure that there is about 1cm of the Stabilizer part near the node.
And the Stabilizer is not hidden.
The Stabilizer is best to be added one by one, so that the effect will be better when we add the Stabilizer at the back.
After adding it, prepare to adjust the shrinkage.
Now the node will not be affected anymore.
So delete the Stabilizer on both sides and simulate it again.
Then gradually increase the shrinkage to 90.
Remember to simulate it during the process.
When the shrinkage reaches 90,
the Stabilizer will be
Very slow.
And be careful not to overheat the stabilizer.
If the shrinkage is not high enough,
just add the Stabilizer on top.
Then the Stabilizer will be
A little bit more flexible.
Now check the indication of Stabilizer,
using the command,
and the command will be
Exhaust the Stabilizer.
The Stabilizer will be
Then delete the fixed pin of the outer ring and start the simulation.
After simulation, freeze the small piece of board.
Then delete the other side and start the simulation.
Finally, start the simulation again.
The other parts are more suitable for simulation.
If there is a more crooked material like the board in the video, you can freeze other boards.
Then manually adjust the position of this board.
Finally, the production of all the board triangles is completed.
It takes a lot of patience to do the simulation.
You can practice more.
See you in the next video. Bye bye.